# PAULAMI CHAKRABORTY



#### **CONTENT SOLUTIONS**



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **2020 – PRESENT**

#### **Manager, Product Content | Dream11**

Maintaining and growing DAU, revenue from communications, and feature adoption and retention through paid/unpaid campaigns, A/B testing, and product-led interactions.

# 2017 - 2020

# Associate, Content & Social Media | Sportz Interactive

Planning and executing social media campaigns for leading brands including Hotstar, Delhi Capitals, UP Yoddha, and Ultimate Table Tennis.

#### 2015 - 2017

#### Writer & reporter | ZEE (CricketCountry)

Producing cricket articles and news, covering live events and writing reports, and managing social media channels.



### **EDUCATION**

#### **2011 – 2014**

**BSc.** (Physics), Calcutta University



## **PERSONAL SKILL**

Content creation

Creative ideation

Audience insight

# Languages

English, Hindi, Bengali, Korean





#### **ABOUT ME**

COPY AND COFFEE - BANKING ON THESE TWO FOR THE PAST 10 YEARS, I'VE BEEN PROVIDING CREATIVE SOLUTIONS FOR THE VARIOUS BRANDS AND PRODUCTS I HAVE WORKED ON.

MY MOTIVATION LIES IN THINKING FROM A USER'S POV WHILE ALIGNING WITH BUSINESS GOALS.

I AM KNOWN AS THE MOST OUT-OF-THE-BOX THINKER IN THE TEAM, AND AM DRIVEN BY DATA-BACKED RESULTS (AS WELL AS OCCASIONAL APPLAUSE FROM MY PEERS).

